In this video, I'm going to be putting
Grockbot and Hermesbot head-to-head and
showing you guys exactly where I'm using
each of these agents in my workflow. I'm
going to be showing you where I think
Grockbot is better than Hermes agent and
where I think Hermes agent is better
than Grockbot. And I hope that you get
some ideas from this video of how I'm
using these agents that you can apply to
your own life to be able to automate
tasks and get more work done. Okay, so I
want to dive right in getting started
with Grockbot. And I'm not going to be
able to cover all of the agents that I
have because the video would be way too
long. But I can show you guys a couple
of really good examples of bots that I'm
using. I do have a like goal on this
video of 500 likes. So if you haven't
already liked this video, make sure you
do so. First of all, let me just talk
about the structure here. I do use a
chief of staff. So, typically I'm only
messaging this chief of staff who's then
messaging the sub agents and it's a very
good way to manage your agents.
Literally today on the stream I was
using the Grockbot app on my phone and I
just have the Grockbot app open like
this, right? And I can just message the
chief of staff here and I can basically
say, "Hey, can you go ping the
Bridgemind Highlights YouTube manager
and have it respond to any comments that
haven't been responded to?"
So, literally, I just have to go to one
place. I can speak to the agent and then
it's going to be able to ping that agent
that's going to be able to help me
manage one of my YouTube channels. So,
it really is crazy what you can do. And
you can see now another agent coming
through here. Now, another agent is
about So, this is crazy. But this agent
here is the bridge mine QA agent. And
this is a really cool strength of
Rockbot is that you can actually make
updates and it will run updates and use
cursor as a harness. Now, right now it's
using Claude Sonnet 4.5. I have no idea
why it's using that model to make these
updates, but it's using cursor to be
able to make changes to the website. If
you look at this prompt that it was
handed, you can see that Grockbot was
able to QA test the Bridgemind website
and then pull all of the code, be able
to QA test it using its own Linux
machine, find these seven findings, and
then I said, "Okay, proceed with these
updates. You can clone the BirdgeMine
website repo and make the changes as
needed. Review and proceed." And it
launches it in cursor makes the changes
and gets the updates shipped. So you're
literally seeing end to end from QA
testing on its own machine to finding
all of the things that can be improved
to then dispatching tasks to cursor and
then it's going to be able to pull the
changes and test them. So this is
unbelievable endtoend agent workflows.
This agent did just come back with a PR
and I am testing to see if we can make
it so that it launches a better model
like GBT 5.6 Soul when it dispatches to
cursor. And yeah, let's see here. So,
open and cursor and yeah, so now it's
using GPT 5.6 soul. So, I probably just
need to save that as a skill. But this
right here that you're seeing, guys, is
incredible. We have agents that are now
able to QA test in their own isolated
environment and then be able to use a
harness like Cursor to be able to
actually make changes, push PRs, and get
stuff done. It's incredible. So, this is
a really cool strength of Grockbot is
that it does have its own isolated
machine. This right here, it was able to
QA test it. And I do just hook up with
these plugins. So, some of the plugins
that I'm currently using is I do have a
Stripe plugin. I have a Sentry plugin. I
have Gmail connected. I literally the
other day I wiped out I had 24,000
unread emails. I know in my Gmail inbox
and I cleared all of them out with
Grockbot. So, if we go back over here
now to my chief of staff, what's really
nice about the chief of staff structure
is that you can basically just work in
this agent. And you can even see that
right now it's saying, "Hey, this PR is
ready. Do you want to merge it?" And I'm
going to say, "Yeah, let's merge it plus
fix the Amplify canonicals. Let's fix
that." And then I can also message this
and I can say I want you to create a new
agent that is my Sentry assistant that
is going to be able to integrate with
the Bridgemind GitHub account and be
able to review errors and bugs that
we're seeing in Sentry and then pinpoint
exactly what is causing it by reviewing
the code and then making isolated
surgical non-breaking changes using GPT
5.6 six soul in cursor in fixing the
bugs, create this new agent, call it
Bridgemind sentry assistant. So that's
how easy it is to create new bots. So
I'm just going to hand this off to the
chief of staff and then the chief of
staff is going to be able to integrate
with that. It was that Sentry plugin. We
also have an AWS plugin. I have a
Cloudflare plugin. And this is another
strength of Grockbot is there are a ton
of plugins. One password is a plugin.
There are a ton. You can just scroll
down this list. Now, I haven't probably
taken maximum advantage of all the
plugins, but here are just some of the
ones that I have. Now, the Apollo one
has an error in it, but this is a really
cool one as well, where you're actually
able to manage like cold email campaigns
using Grockbot. I've got to show you
guys this. So right now I have an agent
that is called Bridgemind 1 Linux and
this one is currently QA testing
Bridgemind 1 on this Linux machine and
it just found a bug. So it put in a
super long name for the agent and you
guys saw it. It was testing to see what
does the UI design look like when
there's a super long name for an agent
and you could see that it's really
testing the edge cases. So, it's
unbelievable that Grockbot is this good.
This agent is doing something really
cool that I think is worth sharing. So,
Grockbot can actually take actions on
your local machine as well. So literally
what this agent is now doing is it's
running commands on my computer which is
very useful because if Grockbot could
only access that isolated environment
then it would be very difficult to be
able to do anything but now it's showing
something sensitive that I can't share.
But it's pulling in AWS credentials off
of my machine so that it can access my
AWS account and manage AWS
infrastructure. It's insane. I created
another bot and I had this bot literally
go out to my Bridgemind YouTube channel
and then use foul to be able to create
thumbnails for Bridgemind. And guys,
look at what it came back with. So, I
just dropped in a screenshot of myself,
a little mug shot, and it was able to
create this thumbnail using FAL. And
this is incredible because now I'll just
use Grockbot for all Bridgemine
thumbnails in the future. And I can
always now just go back to this bot
which has the skills to be able to do
this. Literally, previously I was using
this workflow using claude code, copying
and pasting over to foul and then
iterating a couple times. Now I'm just
going to be able to use Grockbot. So
with all of this in mind, I hope it
gives you a few ideas of how you can be
using Grockbot. But really the strengths
of Grockbot is this is the most rock
solid reliable agent system that I've
used openclaw. I've been using Hermes
agent and Grockbot is in a complete
league of its own. I don't know if it's
because these other projects are open
source and they are not as incentivized
to make them reliable and make them rock
solid, but one thing is just out of the
box, Grockbot is so reliable. I have not
run into any errors, any bugs, any
issues with Grockbot. It is incredible.
The UI for Grockbot is also insane. I
can use it on my phone. I love the app
on my phone. I can also use it on my
computer. And remember, this is all
synced up. So, all of these agents, like
I literally have that chief of staff
agent and all of the agents that I'm
accessing here on my phone. And I can
open up this computer and it has all of
the same chats. I can open up my
computer here and it has all the same
chats. So, I love the app and the
isolated machine is also really cool
because it allows Grockbot to be able to
run 24/7. If we go back to this agent
here, literally all I told it to do was,
hey, I want you to go to the Bridgemine
YouTube channel and look at the existing
thumbnails on the YouTube channel. And
it did that. I was able to use the
machine, navigate over to the BridgeMind
YouTube channel, take a look at the
thumbnails, and then go from there. And
it didn't interact with anything on my
computer. I love the isolated machine.
One drawback of Grockbot is that you're
locked in to using Grock 4.6 only, and
this is something that a lot of people
are having problems with because you're
locked into using Grock 4.6 six and then
you're also locked in to using your
cursor subscription or your Super Grock
subscription, whatever you have. Now, I
do have Super Grock heavy, so I do get a
lot of usage with Gro 4.6. I personally
have not had usage issues, but I also
get heavily subsidized. So, I'm not sure
if you guys are having problems with the
usage, but I see a lot of people on X
complaining about it because one problem
with Grockbot is that, hey, once you
reach your limits, it's over, bro.
you're done. You're not going to get any
more access to Grockbot. Once you hit
your weekly usage, you're cooked. You
can't use Grockbot anymore. And a lot of
people on X are running into usage
issues. I personally am not. I'm getting
subsidized. So, I don't have a problem
with this. I only was at 1% based off of
all this usage, but I didn't really do
anything that was like token intensive,
if that makes sense. But, if you have a
ton of bots that are running routines
and all this, it's going to become a
problem. But that is one weakness is
that you're using your Grock
subscription and once you reach your
limit, you're done and you're locked to
Grock 4.6. So you can't use quad, you
can't use GPT, you can't use open-
source models. Definitely a problem for
a lot of people. Another thing with
Grockbot is you have limited
customization. With my Hermes agents, I
can pretty much do anything. I can do
whatever I want. I feel like I have a
ton of flexibility and I'll get into
that and show you my Hermes agent setup
here in a second. But with Grockbot, one
thing I notic is you're locked in.
You're tied in to Grock. You're tied in
to whatever they do with the product. It
doesn't feel customizable. It's not open
source. It's closed source. It's a
product. So, I feel like the
customization with Grockbot is very
limited. But with that said, it also
offers a very strong plug-in ecosystem.
It was very easy for me to integrate
with GitHub. It was very easy for me to
integrate with Apollo. It was easy for
me to integrate with Gmail and pretty
much you have ooth flows for all of your
plugins. So whereas Hermes agent, you
have to set it up and there's a really
strong setup process and hard setup
process, whereas with Grockbot, it has
this incredible plug-in ecosystem where
you have these ooth flows that are super
easy to configure your apps and it just
makes it simple. It makes it easy. So
really like the plug-in ecosystem. But
with all that said, let's dive in to
Hermes agent. Okay, so here is my Hermes
bot setup. And this was Hermes response
to Grockbot is that they released Hermes
bot. And if you scroll down here, you
can see I have a ton of these bots.
Okay, I have a bot for Google Ads. I
have a bot for Bridgebench. I have a bot
for a video clipper. And this is one bot
that I want to show you right now
because this is one way that I used
Hermes Agent that was literally insane.
Look at this guys. So, I had this
YouTube channel, right? It's called
Bridgemind Highlights. And if you go
down, I was able to create this video
right here. It's a 13minute YouTube
video that has 5,900 views. And this
video was created, published, like
literally everything with it. The
titles, the description, the thumbnail
that you see, the video itself, it was
all created using this Hermes agent
right here, video clipper. So, I was
able to create a Hermes agent that pulls
down Bridgemine live streams and is able
to create a highlight video that
basically clips the most important parts
of the stream and make a standalone
long- form video from that live stream.
I am running Hermes Agent on my personal
machine. I also have four Hermes agents
on the Mac minis that you see as well as
the DJX Sparks. And one strength of
running it on your machine is that if
the agent runs into any issues, you can
just take over real quick. But one thing
that I wanted to show you guys is that
with Grockbot, the computer that
Grockbot runs on has 126 gigabytes of
storage on the machine. My machine that
you see running here has over a terabyte
of storage. So, for example, like if I
go back to the video clipper, it's able
to pull down a six-hour live stream and
edit it on my machine and then upload
the video and it has no problems with
storage. Now, you could potentially be
using maybe like an S3 bucket with
Grockbot. That's actually something I
want to try is to see if I can get this
same exact workflow working with
Grockbot because if I can do that, then
there's no need for Hermes agent. But
this was a very strong use case of
Hermes agent is to create these videos,
to publish them. It was very impressive
and I was able to get it working very
quickly. Now, one thing that I want to
show you guys which is a huge problem
with Hermes and this is actually a
reliability issue is that Hermes is not
reliable. It's very buggy. And look at
this chat here. So, I'm in the video
clipper chat and if we go up, I actually
told my Hermes agent, hey, I need you to
create another long form video from my
stream from yesterday. And all of a
sudden if you go down there is like
Google ads segment which is crossing an
authenticated account boundary like the
Google ads. Look at this. The Google ads
footage is usable. So it's talking about
Google ads. There is nothing here that
should be about Google ads. And what I
think is happening is I think that
somehow someway there's some weird bug
where with Hermes agents and Hermes
bots, my chats are like mixing up with
one another because this has happened
several times where I'll literally be in
the Google Ads chat, right? And all of a
sudden it starts talking about what one
of the other bots is working on. So it's
a little bit buggy and I find myself
running into a lot of errors and bugs
with Hermes bot. And this is a good
example of it where it's like, why are
you talking about Google Ads right now?
This bot and this agent literally has
nothing to do with Google Ads. We go
back over to the Google Ads agent. Look
at this guys. Even just the app
interface in itself. Do you see how it's
trying to paste in the images from the
Google Ads? This is a problem.
Literally, Hermes bot in the Hermes
desktop app has a problem with rendering
in images in the chat. Because if I go
back over to Grockbot, literally I can
see all the images here in the chat.
It's very simple. I've never had any
bugs with it. And Hermes, it's I feel
like I have to do so much extra work
where it's okay, let me just I need you
to copy these over to my downloads
directory so that I can open them and
review them. I can't even look at these
in the chat because this is hooked up
with my it's hooked up with my codec
subscription, which is one strength of
Hermes is that hey, I can use my codec
subscription with Hermes. That's
actually all I've been using. Which file
should I copy? Send me their names. Even
this right here, like this here is a
problem. Look at this guys. I I'm in
this chat. I'm saying I need you to copy
these over to my downloads directory.
This is very obvious of what I'm trying
to do. It's these images right here. And
then it's which files should I copy? And
so I don't know what's happening. I
don't know what the harness is doing
behind the scenes because obviously it
doesn't have the context of literally
what it just told me. So I find myself
having to then take this and copy and
paste and say these images here. So I
feel like I am doing extra work with
Hermes. It's the harness is not as good.
I I now it says got them. I'll copy them
over and it's like okay just having to
do that extra work. I don't feel like
it's a handoff agent. I can't rely on
Hermes agent like I can rely on
Grockbot. Now here are the images. So
now it's rendering them in. And even
this, I don't know how I feel about
these Google ads, but 50% off your first
3 months of Bridgemind BM50 off purple
gradients all over the place. I don't
know, guys. I don't know how I feel
about this, but you can tell that the
harness just isn't as good. Now, one
thing that I do is this agent here. I
literally just call this the stream
agent. And this agent is able to create
the Bridgemind live streams in Reream.
So you can see day 223 vibe coding an
app until I make a million dollars. AR
$188,000.
So it went over to my Stripe. It found
what the ARR was. It was able to create
this title. It was able to create the
description. And now I can just say yes,
I now want you to create this stream in
Reream. Do not start it yet or anything,
but just create the stream now. So this
is a great strength because this is
going to use my machine. I'm already
logged in to reream. I'm already
authenticated. I don't have to do
anything. It's going to take control of
my browser. It's going to be able to get
this stream created. So, I am just hands
off at this point. This was something
that I would literally have to do
myself, right? So, you can automate a
ton of tasks on your computer with
Hermes. And at this point, I think that
having a Hermes agent on your machine is
very important. If you don't have an
agent that's running on your machine, I
think that you're missing out on a lot.
And that's one thing that differentiates
Hermes and Grockbot is that with Hermes,
hey, I can set this up on my machine. I
can have it take actions on my machine.
With Grockbot, it's in its own isolated
environment, which is good, but it also
doesn't have the ability to take action
on my machine. So, with all of this
said, this is how I look at Hermes
Agent. I think that when you compare
Grockbot and Hermes Agent, Hermes Agent
is the buggier, more unreliable app. I
think that I've run into a ton of
problems with Hermes agent. I've noticed
bugs that just aren't there with
Grockbot. I also think that the Hermes
desktop app is clunkier and weaker. And
if you do want to use Hermes on your
phone or message your agents, you have
to configure them with your own app,
which is you could say that's good
because I can configure it with Discord.
Literally, I just have all of my agents
running in this Discord here. So, I can
ping all my agents at any time, which is
nice. But with Grock, there's no setup.
If you're a complete noob to agents and
you're trying to get started with Hermes
agents, it's just more challenging out
of the box. Down here, I have hard to
configure and set up. It's hard to set
up Hermes agent. If you're a complete
noob getting started with these agents,
Grockbot is the better option. Hermes
agent, I had to set up Discord apps. It
was complicated and yeah, it's just hard
to set up. Now, with that said, I do
think that Hermes Agent is more
customizable than Grockbot. With
Grockbot, you get what you get. Hermes
Agent, it's open source. You can change
things around if you want. I feel like I
can do way more with a Hermes agent.
Like, I can do anything. Where with
Grockbot, it's running on this isolated
machine, I feel like I'm limited in what
I can do. And with Hermes agent, I'm
like, "Yeah, I can pretty much do
anything. If I want to download 50
gigabyte video live stream from YouTube,
I can go do that and then clip it
however I want on my machine. Where with
Grockbot, I would need to do more setup.
I would probably have to set up an S3
bucket, which actually is a good idea. I
want to try that. Another strength of
Hermes agent is that you can run
whatever models you want. With Grockbot,
you're going to be stuck using Grock and
you're stuck using your existing Grock
subscription. With Hermes Agent, I can
configure it with my codec subscription
and use GPT 5.6 Soul. I can use that
until I run out of usage and then if I
run out of usage I can switch it to an
open source model because I do have it
running on the DJX Spark. So I'm like
okay I have way more customizability
with the models that I'm using which is
very nice. So I do give both of these
agents the bridge mine stamp of approval
because I am using them. I think that if
you only use Grockbot, I think that
you're going to run into limitations
with using Grock as the only model you
can access and only being able to access
its isolated machine. I think that
Hermes agent, while it's buggier and
more unreliable, there's just more that
you can do with it. You can set it up
with whatever subscription you want. You
can run local models on it. So, right
now, I think that there's still room for
both. But if I just had to choose, hey,
literally which agent is better,
Grockbot or Hermes agent? I would choose
overall Grockbot as the better agent. I
think that everything that we've talked
about, the UI, the reliability, the
ability to message between agents
running on its own isolated machine out
of the box, the plug-in ecosystem,
Rockbot is just the better agent. But
that doesn't mean that should be the
only agent that you're using. So you
guys can see that I'm using both. I'm
going to continue to explore more with
Grockbot and I'm very excited to see
Grockbot get better, but ultimately I
think that you should be using both. If
you haven't tried out Grockbot, make
sure you do so. And if you haven't tried
out Hermes, make sure you do so. I do
think that this is the new frontier of
AI. I think that Claude Code and Codeex
at some point are just going to go away
most likely and we'll probably be using
agents like this. I was literally QA
testing, making pull requests, merging.
It's literally insane what you can do
with these agents. Now, if you're not
using these agents, that is a problem,
guys. You have to start figuring out how
can I use these agents, not to just code
for me, but literally automate tasks
that I'm doing in my life. If you're not
using them, you have to be using them.
If you're going to choose one or the
other, choose Grockbot. But again, I
recommend getting used to using both and
just exploring and seeing what you can
build with both because these are
changing my life. It's making so many
things so much easier. If you guys have
any questions, please let me know in the
comment section down below or have
anything that you want me to know about
these agent frameworks. I would love to
learn from you guys. So, drop a comment
down below. I'm going to be reading and
responding to every comment on this
video. And if this was helpful to you,
make sure you drop a like on the video.
I do have a like goal of 500 likes. And
subscribe to Bridgemind for more content
like this. And with that being said, I
will see you guys in the future.